Guide to the Hiram Larew literary papers, 1947-2018 MS2225
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Workshops and conferences, 2001-2019; Series 5
  - St. Mary's Poetry Workshop, 2004; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Weymouth Center for the Arts & Humanities, 1997; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Weymouth Center for the Arts & Humanities, 1997; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Woodrow Wilson Visiting Fellows Program, 2019; MS2225 Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Audiovisual materials, 1992-2016, undated; Series 6
  This series contains CDs, DVDs, VHS tapes and cassette tapes of poetry readings, performances, and works by Hiram Larew and other poets. The materials range in date from 1992 to 2016. There is a video recording of the Allen Ginsburg Poetry Awards Ceremony. Also of note is a video recording of the Poet Connection, an advocacy group that promotes diverse voices in poetry which Larew co-founded.
  - Adrift - Barbara Decesare (CD), 2006; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Aesops Eagles and Poems From the Road - Anne Harding Woodworth (CD), 2001; Series 6 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Allen Ginsberg Poetry Awards Ceremony (VHS), 1992; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tapes: Readings, 1992-1999; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tapes: Readings, 1998; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Compact Disks, 2004-2006; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Compact Disks, 2008-2012; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - DVDs, Circa 2009; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Jazz Poetry! Live at Iota Club and Cafe (CD), 2004; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Letter from Italy, 1944: A New American Oratorio (DVD), 2014; Series 6 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - The Poet and the Poem: Hiram Larew (CD), undated; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Poet Connection at Glenarden Cable TV (VHS), undated; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Poetry Alive at Iota: Iota Poetry Series 10th Anniversary (CD), 2005; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Poetry in Black and White - Cliff Bernier & Verniece Turner (CD), 2005; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Radio Fairfax (CD), 2016; MS2225 Series 6 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Road Less Taken (CD), 2001; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - September Song: Poets of Frederick, MD - in Reaction to 9-11 (CD), 2001; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Sojourn With Words: Busboys and Poets (CD), undated; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Talking to Myself - Joanne Stato (CD), 2002; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 3rd Thursday Poetry: Hiram Larew, et al. (DVD), 2016 April 21; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Under the Thunder of Wonderful Songs in the Key of Surf - Susan Beverly (CD), 2003; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Word Up Baltimore: A Poetry Collection (CD), 1997; Series 6 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Photographs, 1947-2007; 2000-2007; Series 7
  This series contains photographs of Hiram Larew and other poets, many from the Washington, DC area. Most of the photographs are candid shots. The materials range in date from 1947-2007, with the bulk of the materials dated from 2000-2007.
  - Photographs, 1947-2007; Series 7 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 1993-1998; MS2225 Series 7 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 2000-2003 (Box 31)